<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>tutorial - Category - Omer&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/categories/tutorial/</link>
        <description>tutorial - Category - Omer&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>omerabdi@pm.me (Omer)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>omerabdi@pm.me (Omer)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 16:29:48 &#43;0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omer-biz.github.io/categories/tutorial/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Mounting and unmounting with dmenu</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/mounting_and_unmounting_with_dmenu/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 16:29:48 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/mounting_and_unmounting_with_dmenu/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mounting and unmounting with dmenu Mounting devices with the mount command is a hassle, at least for me. To mount devices with the mount command you need to be root but if you use any kind of file manager to mount devices you don&rsquo;t need to be root. Have you ever wonder why is that. Well it&rsquo;s simple they use a different kind of command it&rsquo;s called udiskctl here the help.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Pandoc</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/pandoc/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:46:44 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/pandoc/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pandoc Have you ever wanted to write a document, but you hate using applications like MicroSoft Office, Libre Office, Google Docs, or anything of the sorts. Do you want to write your documents just like you write codes, with your code editors perk. I for example use vim and I would have loved, if these application supported vim bindings. Well look no further, you can just use pandoc.
Pandoc is a command-line app which can be used to convert a document of any type to any other type.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Remap Capslock to Escape and Ctrl</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/remap-capslock-to-escape-and-ctrl/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 09:57:46 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/remap-capslock-to-escape-and-ctrl/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Remap Capslock to Escape and Ctrl In this post I&rsquo;m gonna be showing you how I remapped capslock to ctrl when you hold it, and esc when you tap it.
The need for this comes from people using window managers, or keyboard driven text editors like vim, and emacs or just you use the ctrl key a lot and you hate the weird motion you have to do to get to it.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Screenshot with Markdown and Vim Using Scrot</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/screenshot-with-markdown-and-vim-using-scrot/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 18:50:01 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/screenshot-with-markdown-and-vim-using-scrot/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Screenshot with Vim In this post I will show you the easiest way I could come up with for taking screenshots and inserting them to a markdown file while taking notes using Neo(vim).
The title maybe confusing as I couldn&rsquo;t come up with a shorter title myself. If you could come up with a shorter title please contact me.
I faced this problem while I was taking notes through my playing of CTFs and doing pentests.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
