<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Omer&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Omer&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>omerabdi@pm.me (Omer)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>omerabdi@pm.me (Omer)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:48:36 &#43;0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Narnia 6 - OverTheWire</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/narnia-6-overthewire/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 13:48:36 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/narnia-6-overthewire/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Narnia 6 - OverTheWire Introduction This level is all about overflowing into a local variable, specifically to a local function pointer variable. When you run the program without any argument it will exit asking for 2 arguments. These two arguments are mapped or copied to the two local variables on the stack, namely b1, and b2. They are copied using strcpy which we know is not a safe way of copying from user inputs.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Narnia 5 - OverTheWire</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/narnia-5-overthewire/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 12:19:38 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/narnia-5-overthewire/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Narnia 5 - OverTheWire Introduction This level introduces what format string vulnerabilities are. A program is said to have a format string vulnerability if it pass unsensitized user input to one the printf family of functions. These are as follows.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15  #include &lt;stdio.h&gt; int printf(const char *format, ...); int fprintf(FILE *stream, const char *format, ...); int dprintf(int fd, const char *format, .]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>What Is OverTheWire</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/what-is-overthewire/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 10:34:24 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/what-is-overthewire/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is OverTheWire Overthewire is a really good resource for someone really new to cybersecurity to learn about cybersecurity. It has a hands on approach of teaching things. It has what I call Seasons. These so called Seasons are not actually numbered but rather named, and each season has an episode. At least that&rsquo;s how I imagine it in my head.
Each season teaches a different cybersecurity concept. For example season 1 (Bandit) teaches about the Linux Operating System.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Mounting and unmounting with dmenu</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/mounting_and_unmounting_with_dmenu/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 16:29:48 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/mounting_and_unmounting_with_dmenu/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mounting and unmounting with dmenu Mounting devices with the mount command is a hassle, at least for me. To mount devices with the mount command you need to be root but if you use any kind of file manager to mount devices you don&rsquo;t need to be root. Have you ever wonder why is that. Well it&rsquo;s simple they use a different kind of command it&rsquo;s called udiskctl here the help.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How I hacked my first router</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/how_i_hacked_my_first_router/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 21:06:22 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/how_i_hacked_my_first_router/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[How I Hacked My First Router I have never found a real vulnerability in the &ldquo;real world&rdquo; before. I was just playing CTFs and Wargames. One day I was looking through our old stuff, and I stumbled up on this router the ZTE - ZXDSL 831C II, and had heard before that this router has a vulnerability. So I thought this would be the perfect chance. I set it up and started pwning.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Pandoc</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/pandoc/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:46:44 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/pandoc/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pandoc Have you ever wanted to write a document, but you hate using applications like MicroSoft Office, Libre Office, Google Docs, or anything of the sorts. Do you want to write your documents just like you write codes, with your code editors perk. I for example use vim and I would have loved, if these application supported vim bindings. Well look no further, you can just use pandoc.
Pandoc is a command-line app which can be used to convert a document of any type to any other type.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Remap Capslock to Escape and Ctrl</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/remap-capslock-to-escape-and-ctrl/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 09:57:46 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/remap-capslock-to-escape-and-ctrl/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Remap Capslock to Escape and Ctrl In this post I&rsquo;m gonna be showing you how I remapped capslock to ctrl when you hold it, and esc when you tap it.
The need for this comes from people using window managers, or keyboard driven text editors like vim, and emacs or just you use the ctrl key a lot and you hate the weird motion you have to do to get to it.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Screenshot with Markdown and Vim Using Scrot</title>
    <link>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/screenshot-with-markdown-and-vim-using-scrot/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 18:50:01 &#43;0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://omer-biz.github.io/posts/screenshot-with-markdown-and-vim-using-scrot/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Screenshot with Vim In this post I will show you the easiest way I could come up with for taking screenshots and inserting them to a markdown file while taking notes using Neo(vim).
The title maybe confusing as I couldn&rsquo;t come up with a shorter title myself. If you could come up with a shorter title please contact me.
I faced this problem while I was taking notes through my playing of CTFs and doing pentests.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
